



+48 662-651-622



szymon.s@poczta.onet.eu



Poland, Lodz 92-525



08.11.2000 Lodz

# Languages

- Polish: Native language
- English: B2

### **Education**

# 2019 -2022

Bachelor's degree - Business IT, University of Lodz, Poland. Received Rector's Scholarship for academic performance

## Specialized skills

Java, SQL, Spring Framework, Cosmos DB (NoSQL), Hibernate, Git, GitHub, Groovy, REST, Vue.js, React.js, Maven, HTML, Gradle, CSS3, Jira, TypeScript, JavaScript, Oracle, NestJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Docker PostgreSQL, Cypress, XSLT, Apache Kafka

# Szymon Szafoni

Full Stack Developer

### **Professional Summary**

Full Stack Developer with 3.5 years of experience with a track record of developing, enhancing, maintaining software systems. Recognized for a collaborative approach to problem solving and a strong desire to learn and adhere to industry standard.

#### **Work History**

10/2022 - current

# Abiliton Intermediate Software Engineer / SoftServe Poland sp. z o.o., Wroclaw, Poland

- Took part in maintaining and developing authentication and authorization system for medical facilities using Java, OracleDB, JavaScript and XSLT.
- Implemented logic that stopped sending customer notifications and giving false signals based on the integrations used by particular customer as a result it reduced need for SSH sessions and improved team performance.
- ✓ Took part in implementing product enhancement that allowed users to create new enterprise part.
- ✓ Implemented critical fix for one of the authorization workflows which allowed company to increase sales.

06/2022 - 05/2024

# Full Stack Developer / EFS Innovation Polska sp. z o.o., Warsaw, Poland Medical project:

- ✓ Took part in rewriting old medical system for generating medicine leaflets to the newer version using Java, PostgreSQL and React.is.
- ✓ Implemented caching mechanism that improved application performance significantly.
- ✓ Collaborated in team-based, Agile environment to accomplish objectives by deadlines.

#### School project:

✓ Took part in designing and implementing microservice responsible for deleting user data in compliance with GDPR standards for virtual school system using NestJs, MongoDB and Vue.js.

- ✓ Implemented automated tests using Cypress.
- Collaborated in team-based, Agile environment to accomplish objectives by deadlines.

# 06/2021 - 05/2022

## Junior Java Developer / BlueSoft sp. z o.o, Warsaw, Poland

- ✓ Implemented ordering system for shop owners using CosmosDB, Java, Spring WebFlux, Hibernate.
- ✓ Collaborated in team-based, Agile environment to accomplish objectives by deadlines.
- ✓ Used reactive chain programing in microservice architecture.
- Took significant part in creating and implementing product thresholds algorithm which allowed customer to know how much product to order based on historic data coming from external system.

### Certifications

- Course -"JAVA od Podstaw do Eksperta"- 31 hours
- Course -"Git od podstaw dla każdego"- 4 hours
- Course "JavaScript od Podstaw do Eksperta" 12.5 hours
- Course "Java ambitny start. Zbuduj aplikację webową!" 8.5 hours
- Course Apache Kafka Series- Learn Apache Kafka for Begineers v3 –
  8.5 hours

### **Hobbies**

- Football
- Formula 1
- Gaming

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji na aplikowane przeze mnie stanowisko zgodnie z Rozporządzeniem Parlamentu Europejskiego i Rady (UE) z dnia 27 kwietnia 2016 r. w sprawie ochrony osób fizycznych w związku z przetwarzaniem danych osobowych i w sprawie swobodnego przepływu takich danych oraz uchylenia dyrektywy 95/46/WE